<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global City Team Challenge</title>
    <link>https://pages.nist.gov/GCTC/tags/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Global City Team Challenge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2016 - 2017, Global City Team Challenge all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://pages.nist.gov/GCTC/tags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Action Clusters</title>
      <link>https://pages.nist.gov/GCTC/action-clusters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 09:56:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pages.nist.gov/GCTC/action-clusters/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are more than 300 organizations participating in GCTC smart city technology projects, called Action Clusters. These participants include representatives from U.S. cities and states, major cities in other countries, government agencies, private companies, non-profits, universities, hospitals, and a variety of municipal-focused organizations. (More information to be added soon.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table class=&#34;table&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr class=&#34;tableizer-firstrow&#34;&gt;&lt;th&gt;Action Cluster&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Municipal Governments&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Members&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Team Lead Name&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Sector&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Description&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;External Web Site&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;A Smart Crime-Curbing System&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Chattanooga, TN&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Electrical Power Board (EPB), Chattanooga Enterprise Center, CoLab, UTC Police, UTC CSE department&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Li Yang&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Abuja City Integrated Transportation System&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Abuja City, Nigeria&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;NITDA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Bernard Weich&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Advanced Flood Warning and Environmental Awareness System for the City of Rohnert Park (AFWEAR) - IoT Based&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Rohnert Park CA, City of Santa Rosa CA, Sonoma County CA Board of Supervisors&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Sonoma County Water Agency, Center for Environmental Inquiry, Sonoma State University Engineering Science Department, Sonoma State University Facilities, Intel, IBM, Dew Mobility- a division of Dew Software Inc.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Shivakumar Mathapathi, Farid Farahmand&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Air Quality Monitoring in London&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Greenwich Borough (UK)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Greenwich Borough, GSMA, Telefonica, Everimpact, Ordnance Survey, NEC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Mathieu Carlier&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;The Greenwich Borough is deploying an Air Pollution monitoring solution to improve air quality for its citizens.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.everimpact.org/&#34;&gt;www.everimpact.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Air Quality Sensing Wherever You Go in Taipei&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Taipei (Taiwan)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ling-Jyh Chen (Academia Sinica); EDIMAX Technology Co., Ltd.;Realtek Semiconductor Corp.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Poh-Shi Ko&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Amsterdam IoT Living Laboratory &amp;amp; Beacon mile&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Amsterdam, Netherlands&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;KPN, IBM, HvA (school) , Sensemakers meetup, Appsterdam meetup, TELE2 ODINE&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Jonathan Carter&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Applying Open Data to inform future Smart City Design&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kansas City, MO&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;PlatIT Impact; Prof. Praveen Rao, University of Missouri, Kansas City; Prof Vladimir Krstic, Director the Kansas City Design Center (KU/KSU)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Dominique Davison&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;BigClouT - Big data meets cloud of things for improving the quality of experience of citizens and visitors&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Grenoble (France), Fujisawa (Japan), Bristol (UK) and Tsukuba (Japan)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;CEA (France); Engineering SpA (Italy); Institute of Communication and Computer Systems (Greece); Lancaster Univ. (UK); Absiskey (France); NTT East Corporation; NTT R&amp;amp;D; Keio University; National Institute of Informatics (NII); University of Tsukuba;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Levent Gürgen&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Busan Smart City: Safe School Zone (OneM2M Platform Based)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Busan, South Korea&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Jason Noh; SK Telecom; Pluxity; Namoo I&amp;amp;C; nTels; DELI-i, etc&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Eunkwang Kim&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Campus Array Node (CAN)/Array of Things (AoT) Network Dual Deployment (&#34;the Project&#34;)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Atlanta, GA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Georgia Tech Research Institute, Argonne National Labs&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Jennifer Clark; Margaret Loper&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Chula Vista Smart Waterfront&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Chula Vista, CA; Port of San Diego, CA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Black &amp;amp; Veatch, Cleantech San Diego, OSIsoft, Qualcomm, Cisco, AT&amp;amp;T, Ed Davalos&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Dennis Gakunga; Michelle White&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Clarity Amidst Chaos: Artificial Intelligence as a Tool for Emergency Responders&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;San Francisco, CA; Alameda County, CA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;One Concern, Inc; San Francisco, CA; Alameda County, CA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ahmad Wani, CEO of One Concern, Inc.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Combating Urban Blight in the New York Capital Region and Mohawk Valley: A Multi-City Building Code Enforcement Information Sharing Pilot Project&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Schenectady, NY; City of Amsterdam, NY; City of Gloversville, NY; City of Troy, NY&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Schenectady NY; University at Albany&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Gary R. McCarthy, Mayor, City of Schenectady NY; Meghan Cook, Program Director; Derek Werthmuller, Director of Technology and Innovation Services, Center for Technology in Government, University at Albany.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Community Traffic Guidance and Control System in Supporting Natural Disaster Emergency Response&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Taichung City, Taiwan&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;National Center for High Performance Computing, National Applied Research Labs, Taiwan. Water resources agency, Taiwan. Private companies working with exiting systems.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Hui-Ming Huang&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Crowdsourcing Preference Data for Transportation Infrastructure&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Atlanta, GA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Georgia Institute of Technology&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Chris LeDantec&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Deployable Communications and Incident Command System for Emergency Response and Disaster Recovery&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Fire Department, City of Denton&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;University of North Texas, Civil Air Patrol, Penn State University, AirRobot, Dean Skidmore, LTE+IoT, Unmanned Experts&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kamesh Namuduri&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Public Safety/Emergency/Disaster/Resilience&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;The Deployable Communication System (DCS) is intended for enabling communications in emergency scenarios when terrestrial infrastructure is not functioning due to natural or man-made disasters. The DCS includes a portable LTE node airlifted by a UAV.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Deploying Real-Time, Multi-Pollutant Sensors (RAMP) in East Liberty&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Pittsburgh, PA; Allegheny County PA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;CMU, the City of Pittsburgh, and Allegheny County&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Albert Presto; R. Subramanian&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Development of IoT based Smart Energy Management System for Smart Green City&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Suwon City, Korea&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Korea Institute of Civil Engineering and Building Technology; Suwon Research Institute&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Suwon Song (Korea Institute of Civil Engineering and Building Technology)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Eindhoven, Brainport Living Lab Smart Mobility&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Helmond, City of Tilburg (The Netherlands); Province of Brabant / Rijkswaterstaat (National Traffic Authority)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Various Companies: a.o. NXP, Tom Tom, TNOSiemens, Dynniq, but also SMEs.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Daniel de Klein&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Eindhoven/CityPulse&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Eindhoven/ Brainport region Eindhoven (Netherlands)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;ATOS International&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Guus Sluijter&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Eindhoven/Strijp-S Smart&amp;amp; Connected Community&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Eindhoven, City of Helmond / Brainport International, Netherlands&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;VolkerWessels Telecom; VolkerWessels iCity&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Johann Beelen&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Envision Austin: Community-Focused, Data-Driven, Mobile-Powered Design &amp;amp; Optimization of Communities and Cities&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Austin, TX&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Vizias, HubCiti , Living PlanIT&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Jay Boisseau; Allison Warner&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Envision Upstate SC (EUSC) 2016-2020 (Name updated 04.07)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Greenville, SC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Greenville County, Pickens County&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Fred Payne&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;EnvyPorto&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Porto (Portugal)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Citibrain (Portugal), InterInnov (France), Technical University Madrid (Spain)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Rui A. Cota, Citibrain; Jacques Magen (InterInnov)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;FIWARE and OASC - Enabling smarter car navigation through cities&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Santander (Spain), Seville (Spain), Porto (Portugal), Antwerpen (Belgium)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Telefonica (Spain), HERE Maps (Germany), Ubiwhere (Portugal), Technical University of Madrid (Spain), UCAN (Spain), Wellness Telecom (Spain), TM Forum (USA), InterInnov (France)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;José Manuel Cantera&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;From Monitoring Underground Infrastructure to Shared IoT Infrastructure: Path toward a Viable Business Model for Cities and Businesses&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Daxing District, Beijing, China&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Washington State University, Prescient Designs, Beijing GTI IOT Technology, EBDA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Andrew Wang; Sandip Roy; Haibo Lv&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Public Safety/Emergency/Disaster/Resilience&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Low-power wide-area wireless sensor networks are deployed for flexible monitoring of diverse underground infrastructure components, including manhole-cover fidelity, toxic gas levels and floodwater in tunnels. A profit-sharing model is created to expand the usage of these wireless sensor networks to other public and private applications.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Galway Smart City: Light Pollution, Air Quality and Noise Monitoring Smart System - IoT Based&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Galway City; Mayo; Sligo; Leitrim; Roscommon&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Dew Mobility - a division of Dew Software, Inc; Insight Centre for Data Analytics at National University of Ireland Galway; Galway City Council&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Shivakumar Mathapathi; Martin Serrano&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Game-based Risk and Loss Management System with integrated Driver Reward Program for the New York City Livery Industry&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;New York, NY&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Qualcomm, Intrinsyc, Orbcomm and multiple communications network providers, insurance companies, universities, large livery leasing companies and livery service providers&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Tim Brogan; Michal Koenig&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;GEO Fencing Predictive Policing solutions to reduce response times for first responders and provide valid data for evidence&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Conover, NC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Paramount Global Holdings, Inc; Dean Skidmore&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kimberly Calhoun&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Public Safety/Emergency/Disaster/Resilience&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Hyperlocal Testbeds for Citizen Science&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Boston, MA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Categorical Informatics; Bitsence; MIT&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Joshua Tan&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Illuminating Smart Cities: Kansas City Runs on IoT Platform&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kansas City, MO&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Sensity Systems, Cisco Systems, Think Big Partners&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Sean Harrington, Amy Lee&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Public Safety/Emergency/Disaster/Resilience&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kansas City, MO (KCMO) and its partners have designed and implemented an IoT platform to develop a smart city network, starting with Kansas City&#39;s streetcar starter line in their Downtown area. Based on this initial site, the team has will implement a model that would make Kansas City the largest smart city network in North America. It will be a city with a new IoT technology platform the is capable of improving particular aspects of city life - such as avoiding traffic jams, finding a parking spot, and getting a Wi-Fi connection at local venues.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Improving Cross Departmental Communications, Operational Efficiencies and Customer Interaction through a Smart Cities Dashboard in the City of Bellevue, WA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Bellevue, WA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;CH2M Hill; Microsoft, Mtuity&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ken Thompson&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City Data Platform/Dashboard&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Develop a water module for the City of Bellevue Smart City Portal using web-service interfaces with existing systems, data analytics, and GIS Visualization dashboard. The Water Module will look at quality, quantity, and cost of water systems.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Interactive optimization of city support for bicycling and other non-motorized transportation&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Oakland, CA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;UC Berkeley; UC Berkeley Real Estate; City of Oakland&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;David Culler; K. Shankari&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;IoT based waste management system - Smart Garbage Monitoring System (SGMS)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of San Leandro, CA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Santa Clara University, Dew Mobility, IBM, Intel; San Leandro Chamber of Commerce; San Leandro Improvement Association (SLIA)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Shivakumar Mathapathi, Prof. Vasu Kadambi&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;IoT Education &amp;amp; Workforce Development&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Montgomery County, MD; Arlington County, VA (Note: This cluster is working with schools in the Kansas City area, but does not have a municipal partner there)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;IoT Dev Labs, Internet of Things DC, Earth Networks, Virginia Tech, Intel, Cisco, Think Big Partners, Texas Instruments, Centeye, George Mason University, community volunteers&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Greg Toth&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;General (Everything else)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Preparing students and the broader workforce for an increasingly sensor-driven environment in smart cities and communities.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://ioteducation.org&#34;&gt;http://ioteducation.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;IoT-Based Healthcare Services&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Daegu City, South Korea&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;South Korea Ministry of Security, ICT, Future Planning; Jongtae Park, Daily Healthcare Demonstration Complex Construction Agency&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Jong-Tae Park&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kaduna State Integrated Learning System&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kaduna North, Zaria &amp;amp; Jama&#39;a Local Governments (Nigeria)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ministry of Budget and Planning; Ministry of Education, Science &amp;amp; Technology; Ministry for Local Government &amp;amp; Chieftaincy Affairs; Ministry of Works &amp;amp; Transport; Ministry for Lands &amp;amp; Country Planning; National Information Technology Development Agency&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Idris Muhammmad&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Leisurity: &#34;Revitalizing the city through smart leisure&#34;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Valencia (Spain), City of Lindale (TX, USA)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Fundación InnDEA Valencia (Spain), City of Lindale (USA), Verizon Wireless (USA), Prodevelop (Spain), Visiona (Spain), Technical University of Madrid (Spain), InterInnov (France)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Paula Llobet&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Lindale - The Genius City Mixed Use Development&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Lindale, TX&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Gregory Brown, Advanced Solutions Architect, Verizon Wireless; Lindale CDC LLC; Pink Pistol; Tyler Junior College&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Craig Lindholm&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;LinkNYC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;New York, NY&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Qualcomm Incorporated, Intersection, and CiviQ Smartscapes&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Al Jenkins; Michal Koenig&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;MAGIC Smart Home/Smart Community Project&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;The City of Westminster, MD&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;The Mid-Atlantic Gigabit Innovation Collaboratory (MAGIC); Target Community and Educational Services; Westminster Security Company; K4Connect; EntryPoint Networks; The City of Westminster; Ting; Intel; Carroll Hospital; LifeBridge&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Robert Wack&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Healthcare&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;A multi-partner collaboration demonstrating a variety of broadband enabled technologies in a residential setting; gathers a wide variety of data, provides intelligent monitoring, analysis, and alerting, to make a measurable positive impact on the quality of life of residents; combines telemedicine and in-home monitoring and controls, to decrease: Emergency Department visits, unplanned medical appointments, staff time spent on unplanned medical care; initial study population of medically fragile adults with intellectual disabilities will eventually generalize to wider population of elderly, aging in place, medically fragile, and chronic disease management populations.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.magicinc.org/smart-home-project/&#34;&gt;http://www.magicinc.org/smart-home-project/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Microgrid Cloud: An IoT-enabled Integrative Framework for Community Microgrid Monitoring, Analytics and Optimization&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Hartford, CT, Town of Windham, CT&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;UConn, CCAT (Connecticut Center for Advanced Technology)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Peng Zhang&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Mobi Microgrids: Sustainable, resilient, mobile power for today&#39;s challenges and tomorrow&#39;s disasters&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;San Francisco, CA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;FreeWire Technologies; San Francisco Department of Emergency Management; The Salvation Army&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Torben Spitzer (FreeWire), Arcady Sosinov (FreeWire), Mike Dayton (SF DEM), John McKnight (Salvation Army)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Public Safety/Emergency/Disaster/Resilience&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;The Mobi Microgrid project aims to support city resilience and emergency response efforts from the ground up. FreeWire has designed an intelligent, mobile battery storage system that is reliable, maintenance-free, and powerful enough for almost any municipal use case. The Mobi replaces non-connected and outdated diesel generators, which are commonly used as emergency response equipment. Cities and agencies will be able to respond quickly to emergency situations, using the Mobi to set up and run silent, clean, and resilient microgrids for mobile kitchens, shelters, and even medical facilities. During non-emergency situations, cities will also be able to utilize otherwise unused assets for smart grid and smart transportation applications. The cornerstones of the project are the FreeWire Mobi, a connected battery solution, and FreeWire&#39;s AMP software, an intelligence layer with modern asset management functionality. In this project, FreeWire will work with the City of San Francisco&#39;s Department of Emergency Management to deploy Mobi Microgrids for The Salvation Army&#39;s emergency preparedness and disaster recovery efforts, including canteens and shelters around the city.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.freewiretech.com/mobile-power/&#34;&gt;https://www.freewiretech.com/mobile-power/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Multi-Time Scale Logistical Scheduling, Maintenance and Dispatch engine for emergency services, Name update Integrated Analytics and Scheduling of Emergency Responders Under Uncertainty&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Nashville TN Fire Department&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Vanderbilt University&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Gautam Biswas; Abhishek Dubey; Eugene Vorobeychik&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;NC RIoT Intelligence Led Public Safety (ILPS)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Police, Fire Department and EMS from City of Raleigh, Town of Wake Forest and City of Cary. State of NC FirstNet&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Wireless Research Center of North Carolina, NC RIoT, North Carolina State University, ASSIST, Smashing Boxes, ST Micro, SAS, Connected Development, NC Department of Information Technology, Broadband Infrastructure Office, FirstNet NC Program&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Larry Steffann&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Next Generation, Resilient Warning Systems for Tornados and Flash Floods&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;North Central Texas Council of Governments; City of Midlothian, TX; City of Fort Wort, TX&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;University of Massachusetts, Colorado State University, North Central Texas Council of Governments&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Brenda Philips; V. Chandrasekar; Michael Zink&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Non-Revenue Water Monitoring and Reduction Using Advanced LTE Communications , Gwinnet County Department of Water Resources&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Gwinnett County Regional Water Authority&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Qualcomm, AT&amp;amp;T, Neptune Meters, Capstone Meters, Trimble/Telog, Krohne, Fathom&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ken Thompson&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Energy/Water/Waste Management&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Design and Pilot an innovative approach to identifying and controlling non-revenue water using Advance Netering Infrastructure, Pressure Transient Sensors, Data&amp;nbsp; Analytics, and visualization spatial dashboard&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;OPEN Data and Predictive Analytics in the City of Glasgow.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Glasgow, Edinburgh, Perth, Stirling, Dundee and Inverness (Scotland)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;IDE-International; Glasgow City Centre Retailers Association; Glasgow Chamber of Commerce; University of Strathclyde; Scottish Enterprise / Scottish Development International&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ross Hamilton&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Open platform for scalable and multi-domain IoT applications for smart cities (previously: Prevention of environmental disasters in the city through data mining)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Genoa Municipality (Italy); Milan Municipality (Italy); Torino Municipality (Italy(&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Engineering Ingegneria Informatica SpA (Italy); ENEA - Italian national Agency for new technologies, energy and sustainable economic development (Italy); FGB; ISMB; Bocconi University - IEFE - Center for Research on Energy and Environmental Economics and Policy (Italy); Integrated Planning Policy and Regulation Action Cluster - European Innovation Partnership for Smart cities (EU)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Paolo Castiglieri, Comune di Genova&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;OpenMove, plug&amp;amp;play platform for mobile ticketing&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Trento (Italy) and the entire province of Trento&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;OpenMove (Italy), Technical University of Madrid (Spain), InterInnov (France)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Lorenzo Modena&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;PA 2040 Enhanced CCTV Public Safety&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Washington, DC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;MPD; DDOT; NCPC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Anil Sharma; Troy Icenhour&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;PA2040 Environmental Sensing&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Washington, DC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;MetroLab partners currently include senior administrators at Georgetown, George Washington, American, Howard and UDC.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Don DuRousseau; , Kenneth Walton&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;PA2040 Smart Parking (renamed on 5/23/2016, previously Smart DC Data Hub Kiosks)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Washington, DC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Golden Triangle BID; Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;David Koch&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Platform for Enabling optimal Multi-Modal Transportation Planning Service&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Nashville TN&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Vanderbilt Univ, Nashville MTA, Siemens Corporate Technology&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Abhishek Dubey, Gautam Biswas, Doug Schmidt, Vanderbilt University; Martin Lehofer, Siemens, CT&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Portland: Connected Intelligent Transportation&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Portland Oregon, Porto Portugal&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Portland, Portland State University, the Technology Association of Oregon, INTEL, the IBI Group, NetCity, urban.systems, OpenBike, DKS, Seaborne, Sera Architects, Urbi, Ubiware, Pangea Motors, InterInnov (France), Technical University Madrid (Spain)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Skip Newberry, Wilfred Pinfold&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Transportation&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;REAL TIME RESILIENCE - Resilience data treatment tools towards Real Time decisions making.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Genoa (Italy), City of Florence (Italy), City of Bari (Italy)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Leonardo Finmeccanica S.p.A. (Italy); CIMA Research Foundation - International Centre on environmental monitoring (Italy); ENEA - Italian national Agency for new technologies, energy and sustainable economic development (Italy); Integrated Planning Policy and Regulation Action Cluster - European Innovation Partnership for Smart cities (EU)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Paolo Castiglieri&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Recycle Please!&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Austin, TX&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Open Austin, Reduces, Vizias&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Derek Sinns; Marco Pineda&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Reducing the Frequency and Morbidity of Pediatric Asthma Attacks&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Dayton &amp;amp; Montgomery County OH; Cuyahoga County, OH&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Dayton Children&#39;s Hospital, OneCommunity&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Marv Schwartz&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;ROSE - Real Time Operational Smart Grid for Europe&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Municipality of Genova (Italy)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Maps s.p.a. (Italy); Genova University (Savona Campus Energy Grid); ENEA - National Agency for new technologies, energy and sustainable economic development - Italy; ENEL www.enel.it; Clarify Austin http://clarify.io/; Integrated Planning Policy and Regulation Action Cluster - European Innovation Partnership for Smart cities (EU)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Giuseppe Franceschelli; Sabatino Gallotta&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Looking info into: https://www.dropbox.com/s/kqef3und0lw2xyt/Presentation%20ROSE.ppsx?dl=0&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Safe Community Awareness and Alerting Network (SCALE)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Montgomery County, MD&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Intel, IBM, Senseware, Sigfox, IoT Dev Labs, Victory Housing, UC Irvine, University of Texas Dallas, N5 Sensors, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Dan Hoffman, Director, Thingstitute; Brandon Bedford&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Safe Town of Shirahama: Preparing for Disasters with Resilient Communication Platform &#34;NerveNet&#34;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Shirahama Town, Wakayama Prefecture, Japan&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Shirahama Town (Japan), NICT (Japan), HIRAKAWA HEWTECH Corporation (Japan), Nassua Solutions Corporation (Japan)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Masugi Inoue&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;This project is deploying a resilient communication platform called NerveNet to secure local communications and connectivity to the&amp;nbsp;Internet even if the town is hit by&amp;nbsp;huge earthquakes and tsunamis.&amp;nbsp;In order to sustain this system, Nervenet is used as a public Wi-Fi at ordinaly times in this project.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Saitama Smart Town:&amp;nbsp;Smart Community Information Platform for Providing Future Town Services&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Saitama, Saitama, Japan&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Hiroaki Nishi, Keio University; Toru Namerikawa, Keio University; Ryogo Kubo, Keio University; Yusuke Nakajima, Kougakuin University; Kanae Matsui, Tokyo Denki University; Kazuyuki Minato, AEON Retailing; Akito Fujita, IIJ-II; Nobuyuki Ariyama, Saitama City; Yuki Okamoto, Misono Town Management; Kazuya Suetsugu, Misono Town Management; Sadahide Morioka, Misono Town Management; Perry Yang GeorgiaTech; Ellen Yi-Luen Do GeorgiaTech; Prof.Joshi（Georgia Institute of Technology); Dr. Hendrik（IBM T.J. Watson Research Center)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Hiroaki Nishi&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;General (Everything else)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;UDCMi is a Smart Community/Smart Town project of 230-hectare area of Misono in Saitama City and is going to provide Smart Town services for 32,000 residents. In UDCMi, Smart Houses, BLE and Wi-Fi area infrastructures, town monitoring systems, smart energy, smart mobility, and health servicers will be provided. This project is supported by a consortium consists of retailing information and service (AEON), security service (SECOM), data management platform (Keio Univ, IBM), town signage (HITACHI), medical care (TANITA and local hospitals), and other information and services. UDCMi develops Smart Community Information Platform (SCIP) for achieving security and privacy in smart city data management and providing smart city data services considering time and privacy critical problems.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.misono-tm.org&#34;&gt;http://www.misono-tm.org&lt;/a&gt; (In Japanese)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Security System to checkmate activities and proper care of Internally Displaced Persons (IDPs) a.k.a IoT - based IDP Tracking and Monitoring System&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Jalingo Local Government; Ardo-Kola Local Government; Bali Local Government; Gassol Local Government; Ibi Local Government; Wukari Local Government; Takum Local Government&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Bernard Kijie Ewah, Head, E-Government, National Information Technology Development Agency, 28, Port Harcourt Crescent, Area 11, Abuja, Nigeria; Cosmas Ayakudo, Landgate Consultancy Ltd. ; IDEAs Hub, NIGERIA, IBM&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Grace Amaefula&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Public Safety/Emergency/Disaster/Resilience&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;This project aims to provide a lasting solution to the problem of Internally Displaced Persons by tackling the issue from three perspectives, 1. Pre-displacement where we understudy the causes of conflicts that lead to IDPs, and try to profer solutions to them, 2. During displacement where we capture the scene of conflict and attempt to minimize losses by alerting relevant bodies and 3. Post displacement where we bring together all the displaced persons and track how they are being managed, assisted and resettled to a normal life.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Sense, Report, Act, and Refine: A Smart City Collaboration&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Washington DC;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Enevo; Krumbs; National Institute of Standards and Technologies; Carnegie Melon University; University of California Irvine; DC Business Improvement District Council; Maalka; Victor Stanley; Keep America Beautiful&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Scott Pomeroy&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Sensor-based Measurement of Transportation Management Performance&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Austin, TX&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;The University of Texas at Austin, Center for Transportation Research&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Jennifer Duthie&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Serving the Underserved with IoT Solutions&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Las Vegas, NV&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;PTC; Thingworx; Ingenu; Arrow; Google&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Don Jacobson &amp;amp; Tiana McNeil&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Smart Agriculture&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Montgomery County, MD&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Microsoft, Link Labs, Fibertower, Patton Electronics, Earth Networks, IoT Dev Labs, University of Maryland Baltimore County&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Dan Hoffman, Director, Thingstitute), Brandon Bedford&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Smart and Accessible Transportation Hub&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;NJ Passaic County; NJ Transit; NYC Mayor&#39;s Office for People with Disabilities (MOPD); NYS Commission for the Blind (NYSCB)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;CUNY City College, Rutgers University&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Zhigang Zhu, Jie Gong&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Transportation&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;This GCTC Team aims to systematically investigate a novel cyber-physical infrastructure framework that can effectively and efficiently transform existing transportation hubs into smart facilities. The Smart and Accessible Transportation Hub (SAT-Hub) is capable of providing better location-awareness services (e.g. finding terminals, improving travel experience, obtaining security alters) to the traveling public, especially for the underserved populations including those with visual impairment, Autism Spectrum Disorder (ASD), or simply navigation challenges.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/_hxdXqTVG7I&#34;&gt;https://youtu.be/_hxdXqTVG7I&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Smart Car-Talk&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Daegu City, South Korea&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Korea Automotive Technology Institute(KATECH), Korea Intelligent Automotive Parts(KIAPI), Renault Samsung Motors, Fusion Soft , Intelligent Transport Society of Korea(ITSK), Korea Telecom(KT), LOGIFOCUS, Sambo Motors, Research and Ubiquitous(RnU), Digital Imaging Lab(DILAB), SECO Interface, Radius Mobility Revolution, Infobank, Bayless, Seoul National University(SNU) Big Data Institute, Hanyang University;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Sujin Kwag; Taewoo Lee&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Smart Cities Optimized&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Montgomery County, MD, Greenville, SC, Gwinnett County, GA, Chula Vista, CA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;AT&amp;amp;T, Qualcomm, Intel, GE, IBM, CH2M, Machfu, Black &amp;amp; Veatch, Mactusa, Landwave, MotionLoft, ShotGun Spotter, Mueller Water, Big Belly&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ed Davalos, Ken Duncan&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Smart Cities San Diego (an initiative of Cleantech San Diego)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of San Diego, City of Chula Vista, Pot of San Diego, San Diego International Airport&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Cleantech San Diego, UC San Diego, Qualcomm, Black &amp;amp; Veatch, OSIsoft, GE, SDG&amp;amp;E and others&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Jason Anderson&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;SMART Emergency Medical Teams&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;FairFax County, VA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Fairfax Fire &amp;amp; Rescue, Inova Fairfax Hospital, George Mason University, Inflow Interactive, Newport News, VA, ASC Consulting, USPHS&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Brenda Bannan PhD George Mason University Jeff Segall MA, MBA Inflow Interactive&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Smart Emergency Response System&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;NCTCOG EPD, Tarrant County Fire Service Training Center, Denton Fire Department, Austin Fire Department&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Yan Wan (University of Texas at Arlington); Shengli Fu (University of North Texas); Michael A. Penaluna (Denton Fire Department), Darrel C. Washington (Denton municipal Electric), Molly McFadden (Emergency Preparedness Department of the North Central Texas Council of Governments), Rodney Smith and Steve Keller (Tarrant County Fire Service Training Center), Coitt Kessler and Richard Davis (Austin Fire Department)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Yan Wan (University of Texas at Arlington&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Public Safety/Emergency/Disaster/Resilience&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Smart Emergency Response System (SERS)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Denton, TX&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Denton Fire Department; Fire Services in Nw Public Services Training, a department of Tarrant County College&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Yan Wan; Shengli Fu&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Smart Insight Amsterdam&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Cities of Amsterdam, Enschede, Zaanstad (Netherlands)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Pecan Street, Alliander (Bram Reijnders, Paul Voskuilen), University of Twente, ABN AMRO, Smart City Amsterdam, Zaanstad, Enschede, Overijssel, Kennispark Twente&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Paul Simmeren; Chantal Mas&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Smart Replicable Solutions to Water-Energy Nexus Challenges&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Washington DC; Cleveland, OH&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;University of California, Irvine (Prof. Nalini Venkatasubramanian, Computer Science; Prof. Stanley Grant, Civil and Environmental Engineering); CB&amp;amp;I Federal Services; Roietronics, Senet, Senformatics, Graphet; Information Technology and Engineering LLC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Sudhir Kshirsagar, President, Global Quality Corp.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Energy/Water/Waste Management&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Drinking water, wastewater, stormwater, and sourcewater related sensing, low power wireless wide area communications, edge computing and cloud-based analytics and physically based modeling to reduce sewer discharges , stormwater runoff and pumping energy usage.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Smart Transit Hubs/ B&#39;Smart&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Baltimore, MD&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Baltimore Departments of Transportation, Energy and IT, Baltimore Gas &amp;amp; Electric, Cisco, Verizon, IDC, Universities of Maryland, Old Dominion, Toronto, Greater Baltimore Committee, Baltimore community associations, Maryland Transit Administration&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Jill Sorensen&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Transportation&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Smart street light planning and installation pilot defined by an urban plan to create transit hubs in Baltimore City to improve City safety, high speed internet (public WiFi) access and improved energy efficiency. The transit hubs and corridors between hubs, will prioritize safe and energy efficient passage from hub to hub, and advanced mobility throughout the City.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;SmartAppCity: global mobile solutions for Smart Cities.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Logroño (Spain)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;JIG Internet Consulting (Spain), Get-App Spain, Technical University of Madrid (Spain), InterInnov (France)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ignacio Gurría de la Torre&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;SmartCU - Covenant University Smart City&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ado-Odo/Ota Local Government, Nigeria&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Covenant University, Santa Clara University, Dew Mobility, Intel, IBM&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Aderemi A. Atayero, Tokunbo Ogunfunmi, Shivakumar Mathapathi&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;SmartShuttle - A Scalable and Replicable Architecture for Low Speed Automated Shuttles in Smart Cities&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Columbus, OH; Greenville, SC; City of Portland, OR; City of Boston, MA; Washington DC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;OSU Center for Automotive Research, Mid-Ohio Regional Planning Commission, GE, Cisco, the Idea Foundry, IBM, Easton Town Center, Innova UEV, (Local Motors &#34;partner in discussion&#34;).&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Randy Bowman; Levent Guvenc&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;SMOOTH(2) - Smart Mobile Operation OSU Transportation Hub II&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Columbus, OH&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;OSU Center for Automotive Research, OSU College of Medicine, Mid-Ohio Regional Planning Commission, Battelle, GE, Cisco, the Idea Foundry, IBM, USDOT, Innova UEV (manufacturer of the DASH EV neighborhood electric vehicle)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Randall Bowman; Bilin Aksun Guvenc&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Solar smart charging for electrical vehicle and vehicle for smart charging&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Stedin; municipality of Utrecht (Netherlands)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Elaad, Lomboxnet, GE, Renault, Vidyn, Last Mile Solutions&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Eugenie Lindeman&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;StormSense&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Newport News, VA, City of Virginia Beach, City of Norfolk, City of Hampton, City of Portsmouth, City of Chesapeake, City of Williamsburg, York County, VA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Virginia Institute of Marine Science (VIMS), College of William and Mary, Commonwealth Center for Recurrent Flooding Resilience, State of VA, Department of Health&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Jon Derek Loftis; Andy Stein&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Public Safety/Emergency/Disaster/Resilience&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;The StormSense Project is an inundation forecasting research initiative to advance the field of emergency preparedness for flooding resulting from storm surge, rain, and tides. The scope of the project encompasses the interests of coastal local governments wishing to enhance their emergency preparedness via a network of &#39;Internet of Things&#39; (IoT)-enabled water level sensors, collaborating with the hydrodynamic flood modeling and forecasting capabilities of the Virginia Institute of Marine Science (VIMS) and their VIMS TideWatch Network.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://stormsense.com&#34;&gt;http://stormsense.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Sustainable Transportation through Ridesharing using Urban Electric Vehicles (Sustainable Transportation through Ride Sharing)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Madison, City of Monona, UW-Madison campus (CIO&#39;s office)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;University of Wisconsin-Madison, Innova&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Suman Banerjee&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;The Hague/From vision to smart Solution&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of The Hague, Netherlands&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;KPN&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Pim Stevens&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;The Hague: 2 citizen engagement big data applications&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;The Hague, Rotterdam, Leiden, Barendrecht, Dordrecht, Alphen aan de Rijn, Schiedam&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Overmorgen / Dutch-Ates&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Gerwin Hop; Tim Kreukniet&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;The Next Generation Business Emergency Operations Center (NextGen BEOC)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Lafayette, LA; Annapolis, MD&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Informatics Research Institute, University of Louisiana at Lafayette; START Center, University of Maryland; Louisiana Governor&#39;s Office of Homeland Security and Emergency Preparedness; Maryland Emergency Management Agency; Siemens Corporation; Steelcase, Incorporated; TCecure, LLC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Michael Dunaway&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Transactive Energy for Smart Cities&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Manila (Philippines)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;MaCT USA, IEEE SA, Copperpillar, Rowan University, University of Philippines, City of Durham (NC), City of Manila (Philippines)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;William J. Miller&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Energy/Water/Waste Management&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;This project utilizes the concepts of Transactive energy to maintain balance of the power grid. It also now offers a means to obtain energy credits in the form of Bitcoin. This capability can benefit people to be able to paid their energy bill but may be used for other transactions.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.powermatcher.us&#34;&gt;http://www.powermatcher.us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Transit Community Spotlight Project&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Montgomery County, MD&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Montgomery County, MD, Thingstitute,&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Dan Hoffman, Director, Thingstitute; Brandon Bedford&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Underground Infrastructure Sensing and Mapping for Smart Maintenance, Sustainability, Usage and Resilience&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Winooski, VT, Burlington, VT&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;BTV Ignite, City of Burlington, VT ; Kardinal Microsystems, University of Vermont; City of Winooski, VT&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Dryver Huston, Tian Xia&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Energy/Water/Waste Management&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Build 3-d maps and information databases of underground infrastructure with combination of ground penetrating radar and combine with networked sensors to better manage operations, maintenance and construction of underground utilities, including water, sewer, electric, energy and telecommunications.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Unraveling the Intersection of Incarceration, Homelessness, and Mental Health&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Washoe County, NV, Wake County, NC, City of Reno, NV&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;SAS&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Jennifer Robinson&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Urban waste and cleaning service level dashboard&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Guadalajara (Spain)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Valoriza-Grupo Sacyr (Spain), Telefonica (Spain), Technical University of Madrid (Spain), InterInnov (France)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Javier Paniagua&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;User-centered Heterogeneous Data Fusion for Multi-networked City Mobility, UHDNetCity (Name change 04.07)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Tallahassee, FL&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Florida State University, Internet2 , StanTec&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Reza Arghandeh, Florida State University; Eren Ozguven, Florida State University&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
 &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;WiseTown: web information stream enhancer city dashboard&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City of Perugia (Italy)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;TeamDev (Italy), Fiware Foundation, University of Perugia (Italy)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Andrea Cruciani, TeamDev &amp;amp; Fiware Foundation;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;City Data Platform/Dashboard&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;WiseTown is a cloud ecosystem for the advanced management of relationship between citizens and local government with regard to urban quality, safety and shared planning that integrates social networks, open data and IoT. It provides Decision Support System, Spatial Analysis, Forecasts and analytics other than vertical solutions to manage participative and inclusive processes. &#34;We like Smart Cities but we prefer Wise Towns&#34;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://wise.town/&#34;&gt;http://wise.town/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>